Well, everybody knows me, I’m Anna Hayes and I’m your local representative of the Guardian Alliance,
which is a group of beings that come from other dimensional systems,
but also other systems of our 3rd dimension.
Some of them are extra-terrestrial, some of them are meta-terrestrial and some of them are  ultra-terrestrial,
which means they’re completely outside of the framework of time and space, as we know it.
It’s a large group that I speak for, and I have been a student of this group since childhood.
And, I’m here this evening to share with you some of things that I have learned,
and I’m hoping to give you something that you can take home with you, some information that can help you,
perhaps, to understand a little bit better what you’re consciousness is about,
what the experience of other dimensional beings and your relationship to them is about.
And, give you some practical tips on how you can take the knowledge of understanding your bio-energetic system
and use it to begin to accelerate the process of your own evolution, both spiritually and biologically.
Now, a lot of people think that spiritual evolution and biological evolution are 2 separate things.
I always thought that, and I think differently now because of what I have been taught by the Guardian Alliance.
They introduced me to something called the “Science of Keylonta”.
And I first asked them, “what is that?” And they said,
“Well, it can be simply defined as the Science of Light, Sound, the sub-conscious symbol codes and the base codes of matter”.
I was like, "Ok, light and sound I understand…these code things, I don’t know what they are at all”.
So, I asked questions and I got many answers, all sorts of things I never really wanted answers to.
But, Keylonta presents a fascinating perspective on the Human mind, on the Cosmos, on matter,
anti-matter and the relationship between all of those thing.
And I would like to share with you tonight, some of the information I’ve learned about this Science.
And, hopefully, we can grow in our learning together,
because I’m a fellow student of the Guardian Alliance and I have a feeling that our species will be learning this for a very long time.
So, we have to start somewhere…Keylonta seems to be the place to start.
All right, I’m going to use some of my notes to help me.
Basically, first question is, “What is Keylonta?”  Before everybody looks at this,
and there’s people in the group who’ve had a little bit of exposure to this,
and I would like to ask “what is Keylonta,
from the information that the people who’ve heard about it have got,
who would like to put a little into “what Keylonta, to your understanding right now?”
Can you help me?
Well, I think it’s basically working with the life force energy of the universe.
It’s also consciously working with it and working with the symbols and codes ok,
that help that  Soul accretion process that we talked about.
And, it’s done with light and it’s done with sound, and it’s done by activating the chakras, ok, using these technologies.
And, you know, it’s not only good to understand it intellectually,
but we need to be activating it so we can experience this stuff first hand.
So, it’s kind of like, you know, a quick overview of…”
That’s very good, it touches on many of the basics of Keylonta.
Is there anybody else that’s read or heard anything about Keylonta that would like to put anything in on that?
I know that…
I was going to say that my understanding of Keylonta,
where we can use light, color and anything that is electrified, may help heal people in the future.
As we have seen some experiences of say, Dr. Robert Becker on growing limbs,
which he was successful on frogs after he cut the limb and the limbs grew…provided the electrical potential of the limbs,
changed from a positive zero to negative, and that causes the frog limb to grow into a normal, just like the salamander.
I believe that in the future, Keylonta, my understanding of Keylonta,
will be same line, and being in the field of medicine.
They’re going to be very interested in that, especially in trauma surgery, and orthopedics.
Keylonta has many, many healing applications.
In fact, in has healing applications across the board,
in everything that effects our Universe and our society and our personhood.
Because, the real core of Keylonta is it’s a Science of Consciousness and a Science of Creation,
it’s the underlying structures of what matter is created from.
It is the underlying structure of consciousness, so it is not something you can learn in one night, by the way (chuckles),
but there are some other things that Keylonta also is.
And, I prepared this for both of us, so I can go down the list for myself,
and also you can read along if you like.  It is…
Hold it up higher?
Ok, it is the Science of Creation and Consciousness.
It’s the Science of macrocosmic and microcosmic interrelationships.
It’s the Science of Energy Dynamics through which matter forms and consciousness manifests.
It’s the Science of biological, physical and consciousness spiritual evolution.
That’s not all
It is the Science of Humanity’s relationship to its Source and the Cosmos.
It is the Science of construction, perception and potentials of the Human organism and consciousness.
It is the Science of the structure of multi-dimensional universe and Humanity’s multi-dimensional identity,
and Humanity’s relationship to other sentient life forms within the multi-dimensional universe.
Keylonta is all these things and more.
It is the Science of the Human Soul and the Family Tree of Consciousness out of which all of us emerged,
which is something not too many scientists know here.
That sounds like something that would be found more so in the realms of religions or churches,
but in truth there is not a difference between science and religion, we only perceive it to be, here.
Science does has a Soul that it hasn’t found yet and Keylonta is the place where it can begin to find its Soul.
Ok, it is the Science of DNA activation, genetic imprinting, cellular memory and transmutation of form.
Through understanding the dynamics of Keylonta, we can literally change the way our DNA operates.
And DNA governs the structure of our physical body, and our physical body will determine what type of consciousness we are able to bring into our minds,
our conscious minds while we’re here.  There’s an intimate connection between Spirit, your spiritual aspect, or your higher dimensional aspects,
and consciousness moving through the body.  Because, you can be…you can have a wonderful level of development of consciousness in the higher dimensions,
but if you have a neurological structure that is not able to handle the current of all the electrical information,
you won’t have access to it on a conscious level.
So, the Science of Keylonta gives us tools and understanding of our parts enough,
that we can start to expand the potentials of our body,
so we can bring in more of our consciousness and awareness,
so we can bring in more of our Soul into manifestation, here.
Ok, Keylonta is the Science of dimensional ascension, teleportation, bi-location and regeneration of identity.
For once you understand how to play with the little particles that you’re composed of,
these units of consciousness that Keylonta will teach you about, things like teleportation will come easily to you.
You won’t need a machine to do it, because you’ll know how to change the vibrational rate of your molecular structure.
Do I know how to do this yet?  No, but I’m first in line as far as wanting to learn.
And that’s…we’re getting the foundation of what one day,
if we work with these tools, will teach us how to do these things.
There are extra-terrestrial races that are in biologies…they’re not just meta-terrestrials that don’t have bodies any more,
they are in bodies…who know this science and who are able to manifest and de-manifest at will.
They are able to walk through solid objects, they are able to travel through time with no problem at all,
things that seem only science fiction has. It’s because they understand the principles of Keylontic Science.
Now, if we get a little more scientific about the whole thing,
Keylontic Science explores the dynamics of time, space and matter…
How those realities of our externalized reality are created.
What are they really?  Where do they come from?  Are they what they appear to be?
Some of these questions will be answered through Keylontic Science.
We will find that time is not linear, as we perceive it to be; it’s simultaneous in nature.
We will find that space all takes place in something called non-space.
You’ll find that matter is actually an illusion, a holographic illusion,
created by the refraction of energy particles and light and sound frequencies.
We will find that things are much different than our 5 senses tell us they are, when we begin to explore Keylonta.
Ok, it is the Science of ultra-micro particle and anti-particle dynamics.
It is the Science of 12 Human Senses, not just the 5.
And, basically, it is the Science of Light, Sound, Sub-conscious Symbol Codes and the Base Codes of Matter.
And now we’ll learn what they are.
We know light and we know sound, but what are sub-conscious symbol codes?
And, what are base codes of matter?
We’ll skip over this section for a while.
This gets into what it can do for us, but I think we’ll get into that at the end.
Now, the reason that I’m reading these is because there is a lot of information and...
if I’m just talking to you off the top of my head, I might miss half of it.
So, I’m going to read it.  If you can read it, that’s all right,
but I don’t think you can because it’s so tiny.
But, it’s more so I’m going to read it you so I don’t lose content that way.
So, if it gets a little annoying, bear with me, at least you will get the information.
All right, there are 6 Primary Elements in the Science of Keylonta.
The First Element are PartikI…that’s a new word.
PartikI are the smallest units of energy in the Cosmos, according to the Guardian Alliance.
They are electro-tonal units of energy identity...
that emanate from a central Source the Guardian Alliance calls the “Yunasai”.
They operate as minute fission/fusion generators.
They create and maintain the electromagnetic frequency fields upon which the universe and all structures built.
They exist within and beyond all matter forms, pre-matter, anti-matter and consciousness.
They form and sustain something called “Morphogenetic Fields” for all forms, sub-particles, etc.
Everything has a Morphogenetic Field.
And, a Morphogenetic Field is a basic energy field, energy structure,
behind its manifest form, that allows that manifest form to keep its shape.
And, everything in the universe, every little particle, sub-particle, has one and PartikI is what they are.
Groups of PartikI form larger Morphogenetic Fields, like the ones Humans would have.
But even PartikI represents a Morphogenetic Field itself,
so they form…you could look at them, if you wanted to,
as little tiny units that are the Morphogenetic Field or form-holding pattern we come out of.
And, we are composed of PartikI; everything is…
the space in the air here is composed of PartikI, our bodies are, our higher consciousness is.
PartikI are Unified Energy Field that runs through the entire Cosmos.
Ok, let’s go back to here…ok, PartikI are units of electro-tonal consciousness.
They are the organizational intelligence within all things.
In the Spiritual terms, they are the living units of conscious identity and energy,
particles of the consciousness of the Yunasai…which some people call “God”.
We are made of these things.  People think God is somewhere out there some place away from us…
we are made of the substance of which that Being is, because PartikI are not just energy units,
they’re energy identity units; they are conscious.
And, they have consciousness that they will group to form different types of consciousness and awareness.
They don’t think in terms like we do, but we think because we are composed of them.
So, in Spiritual terms, the PartikI are our connection and continual connection to a centralized Source...
that we may call God if we’re comfortable with that.
And, if not, the Yunasai works…it’s an energy identity that is a central Source of creation,
and we take place within it.
It’s not out there somewhere; all of reality is taking place within it.
And, this is one of the things you’ll learn in Keylonta.
You will learn the scientific parts of it, which a lot of spiritual people go,
“oh, that’s not important”…
then you’ll learn the spiritual parts of it that a lot of scientific people say,
“Oh, that can’t be because spirit’s not real”.
Hopefully, through Keylontic Science, we can learn that, yes,
spirituality and our spiritual identity is as real as the identity of our leg or our arm.
They are the same substance, they are composed of the same particles, and those particles are PartikI.
Ok, now there are 2 types of sub-particles that are formed from the PartikI.
First one, we call Particum, ok, it is a PartikI unit, it’s considered a PartikI,
but the Particum PartikI is slower moving and it contains half of the electro-tonal,
which is electrified sound thrust or force, of its twin.
So, we have Particum and the Particum has a twin.
The Particum moves half as fast, it pulsates half as fast as its twin does.
The PartikI is a sub-unit…the Particum is a sub-unit of the PartikI- they make up particles in our universe.
They are the little tiny units that make up our sub-atomic particles in the smallest known particles that we would have,
would be composed of Particum PartikI, all right.
There is another type of PartikI that are called PartikA.
The PartikA are anti-particles to the particles that we are composed of.
This implies the existence of a parallel universe,
a parallel self- any form here is a Particum form and it will have its own reflection that moves twice as fast,
vibrates twice as fast, in parallel dimensional system, parallel universal system.
We have 15-dimensions in our system and so does the parallel universe.
And, it’s not like they’re way over there some place in another universe far, far away…
these two universes are intimately intertwined, they are taking place in the same space,
but on different pulses of consciousness.
So, we perceive one set of pulses over here and we don’t see their set and vice versa.
Ok, now, let’s see, PartikI cycle.
The Guardians call this “Cycling”.
The PartikI unit is a unit of electro-tonal thrust that comes out of the Yunasai
because it gets projected into the 15-dimensional system, ok.
When it intersects with the 15-dimensional system,
it under goes fission and it breaks apart and replicates itself.
So, it creates…starts out as one, undergoes fission when it hits the frequency bands of the 15-dimensional system and...
then it replicates itself and the original breaks apart, ok.
So, now the original pattern of that tone remains in the replication, so it’s never gone, ok.
The one that broke up first, the replicable is the original pattern,
the one that came first breaks up into 2 pieces,
the Particum and the PartikA- they are created at the same time,
ok, they flash on, one in our universe and one in the parallel universe.
And, our particles…we’re made of an infinite number of them compose our bodies,
but this is what they are doing so fast that we can’t perceive it.
So, they break up into the PartikA and the Particum,
they manifest into the dimensional fields and then because this one,
the PartikA has twice the amount of thrust or force,
and it’s moving away from the morphogenetic field just like this one is,
it starts to tow the Particum- it makes it spin reverse direction and go back to fuse with the morphogenetic field.
So, the Particum particle here flashes off in our universe and it goes back into the morphogenetic field,
it expands the morphogenetic field, adding to it,
then this becomes more of a thrust than what the PartikA is.
So, it pulls the PartikA, makes it spin,
pulls the PartikA anti-particle back in and it fuses with the Particum particle inside of the morphogenetic field.
Now, both our particle and our anti-particle have both flashed off, we have disappeared momentarily.
Then, this act, as they fuse, it creates…
as we know when something fuses it releases a burst of energy,
it sends a quarter of its thrust back toward the Yunasai,
creating something called a “backflow”,
which is a current that pulls away from the dimensional matrix that we’re in ok.
So, it would be the current that would take us back home to God, if you want to look at it that way.
When it creates the backflow, that sets off another act of fission within the morphogenetic field and again,
the ones that had come together will start to cycle again and it’ll do this again, and they’ll break apart again.
So, they’re constantly flashing on together, then the particle flashes off, the anti-particle flashes off,
they replicate, create a backflow and flash on again.
And, this is happening so fast, I believe the particles…
what …I believe it was 3/100ths of second in the 3rd dimensional particles...
and some of them are much, much faster than that in the higher dimensional fields.
So, we are composed of these structures.
Most of us have no idea we’re composed of these structures and most of us don’t know that we flash on and off.
Where do we go in between these flashes, was my first question.
If I’m flashing on and off and it’s happening,
you know, too fast for my senses to see, where am I going?
You know, when I de-manifest am I gone or what?
No, we return to our original pattern, the morphogenetic field out of which we came,
our original identity that has all of our parts in it and all possible versions of our parts.
Our…all right, in the 15-dimensional Matrix…
which we’re not going to go into it too heavily this time or I’ll never get to the end of what I want to get into,
but the morphogenetic field for the particles that make up say, our bodies, these are d-1 particles,
1st dimensional particles, they would have their morphogenetic field in d-15.
Our, what we call our “emotional bodies”, or, it’s actually our “elemental body”,
the complex elements that form the matter in our bodies, that help to form it,
that is our 2nd dimensional aspect of PartikI, or Particum in our universe.
The morphogenetic field for that is in d-14, so there is a correlation
between the levels of our...
our PartikI here and where our morphogenetic field is in the higher dimensions.
And, we’ll get into that in another little one.
But, it’s enough to know that we’re made of these things, that most people don’t even know exist yet.
And, they hold the key to our consciousness and our perception of matter, space and time.
The 2nd Primary Element of Keylontic Science is a PartikI grid,
and this brings it a little bit home, brings it down to where we can understand it a little bit more.
It’s something that we have and it’s a grid, ok. A PartikI grid is composed of PartikI units.
In our system there is a Particum grid, it’s made of the Particum particles.
In the parallel universe it’s a PartikA grid.
But, what the PartikI grid, whichever side it’s on, is…it’s a grouping of PartikI.
PartikI group by like polarization.
That means Particum will group together and PartikA will group together to form more complex structures.
The first thing they’ll form are strands.
They form strands of electro-tonal energy units.
Those strands group to form grids.
If you take strands and cross them this way and this way and this way, you get what looks like a little carpet of light.
it’s made of little fibers of light and that is the Unified Field of Energy that exists within everything and through everything,
and connects us directly into our Source of which we emerge.
It connects us directly to the Yunasai. It connects us to each other, ok.
So, the PartikI grid is simply…you can look at it as a carpet of light and sound.
It’s invisible to our perceptions, but it exists beneath all matter forms and all forms of consciousness.
Ok, let’s see, ok, here we have the Cosmos represents a massive PartikI grid,
which serves as the Unified Field of Energy Substance within which all things exist and are interconnected.
All beings and matter forms have personal PartikI grids,
which are formed within the grid of the Unified Field.
Energy and Identity perpetually circulate from the Yunasai into the dimensional systems and...
back again through the electromagnetic fabric of the PartikI grids.